Guide to the Emilie F. Miller papers, 1987-1991
George Mason University Libraries
- Emilie F.Miller Collection
  - Announcement of Candidacy for Re-election May 8,1991 (Folder 5, Box 32)
  - Commission on the University in the 20th Century August 17,1989 (Folder 6, Box 32)
  - Autographed Program [signed by Birch Bayh] (Folder 7, Box 32)
  - Clozaril [clozapine] - New Hope for Schizophrenic Patients [1 of 4] 1990-1991 (Folder 8, Box 32)
  - Clozaril [clozapine] - New Hope for Schizophrenic Patients [2 of 4] 1990-1991 (Folder 9, Box 32)
  - Clozaril [clozapine] - New Hope for Schizophrenic Patients [3 of 4] 1990-1991 (Folder 10, Box 32)
  - Clozaril [clozapine] - New Hope for Schizophrenic Patients [4 of 4] 1990-1991 (Folder 11, Box 32)
  - Memberships of Various Organization - Emilie F.Miller 1989 - 1992 (Folder 12, Box 32)
  - The International Children's Festival- Charles S. Robb 1982- 1985 (Folder 13, Box 32)
  - VMI -Alumni Review Sesquicentennial Edition (Folder 1, Box 33)
  - VMI - Spirit (Folder 2, Box 33)
  - Women ,Black and Hispanic State Elected Leaders (Folder 3, Box 33)
  - CAWP Forum for Women State Legislators November 17, 1991 (Folder 4, Box 33)
  - Miller NewsLetter and Campaign Materials (Folder 5, Box 33)
  - Audio and Video Materials - VMI [Kopel Show] (Folder 1, Box 34)
  - Audio and Video Materials - VMI [Channel 56] (Folder 2, Box 34)
  - Audio and Video Materials - VMI [CNN-CrossFire] (Folder 3, Box 34)
  - Audio and Video Materials -[Forum Program 343,Junior Achievement] (Folder 4, Box 34)
  - Audio and Video Materials -Emilie F. Miller for State Senate [No Choice :60 Radio Revised '91] (Folder 5, Box 34)
  - Audio and Video Materials -Emilie F.Miller for State Senate [No Choice :60 Radio produced by Robert.L.Watson '91] (Folder 6, Box 34)
  - Emilie F. Miller - Framed Certificates,Flyers (Box 36)